<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>photography on Henri Kauhanen</title>
    <link>https://hkauhanen.github.io/tags/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in photography on Henri Kauhanen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 21:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hkauhanen.github.io/tags/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bailaora</title>
      <link>https://hkauhanen.github.io/blog/bailaora/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkauhanen.github.io/blog/bailaora/</guid>
      <description>When the pandemic hit, I briefly looked for new inspiration for photography indoors before suddenly losing all passion for the hobby for about two years. This photo is one of the last I took before those two years of photographic depression.
Multiple exposure is a fun technique. Flamenco is a complex dance. I wanted to use the former to try to capture some of the complexity of the latter. So we pushed the living room sofa into a corner and my wife was generous enough to model in front of an ancient Minolta Autocord twin lens reflex camera propped on a tripod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Säntis</title>
      <link>https://hkauhanen.github.io/blog/saentis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkauhanen.github.io/blog/saentis/</guid>
      <description>Looking southward from Konstanz, the mountain of Säntis, some 50 km away in the Appenzell Alps, is clearly visible on most days. It is a modest peak in terms of summit height &amp;ndash; 2502 meters &amp;ndash; but stands very tall amongst its neighbours: Säntis is ultra-prominent, with a topographic prominence of 2021 meters. Having had a glimpse of it practically every day for the past five years, I was curious to get closer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
